David Fertitta



Versatile full stack web developer, with additional experience as a writer, graphic designer and marketer. After spending time working for fast-paced international start-ups and running Beijing's first English language stand-up comedy club, I've since returned to the US and am eaager to merge my new passion of frontend web development with my past experience as experience in design and marketing to create apps that are

Experience

NeuroCann in Denver, CO

FRONT END DEVELOPER

- Worked as part of an agile development team in a React/ Typescript Environment
- Responsible for the creation of intuitive UI features such as Login/ Forgot Password Pages, editable tables, modals and forms.
- Collaborated with design/UX team utilizing Material UI to produce fully responsive sleek designs.
- Utilized JEST to write informative tests and provide better app coverage
- Quickly learned new technologies such as Typescript and Material UI on the job.

TransferThought, in Chicago, IL (Remote)

CONTRACT DEVELOPMENT ASSISTANT

- Assisted in frontend styling changes and bug fixes.
- Learned Vue.js on own time in order to become a more useful asset to the team
- Created demos using in app functionalities to help attract potential customers.

Projects

HOMER (IN PROGRESS)

React JS / Rails

<u>Github FE / Github BE</u>

Chicago Sports themed Wordpress style blog, with full auth built from the ground up using React with hooks and Quill.js for a rich text editor.

BIG LEAGUE EATS

React Native | Rails

Github FE | Github BE

Mobile App which allows users to find and review food vendors near them at MLB stadiums (work in progress).

ANGLER

 $React\ JS\ /\ Rails$

Github FE / Github BE

Demo Video

Fishing app which uses the google maps api to let anglers log fishing results/lures/conditions at any location location.

GLOBAL CRATE DIGGER

Vanilla Javascript / Rails

Github FE | Github BE

App that helped users discover new music from around the world by utilizing clickable SVG maps.

CONTACT

davidj.fertitta@gmail.com 720.425.1286 2840 Blake St. Denver, CO (moving to Austin this summer) www.david-fertitta.com LinkedIn

EDUCATION

2020

GitHub

 $Immersive\ Software\ Engineering\ Bootcamp$

Flatiron School

2006-2010

BA International Stuidies (Minor in Spanish)

Harriet L. Wilkes Honors College, Florida Atl. Univ.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Adobe (inDesign / Photoshop)
- Git
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript
- Jest
- Material UI
- Rails
- React.js
- React Native
- Ruby
- scss
- SQL
- Typescript
- Vue
- Wordpress

OTHER EXPERIENCE

2016-2018

Comedy Club China - President

Organized events and performed various marketing tasks for Beijing's first English language comedy club.

2017-2018

Smart Kids Intl. - Head Curriculum Writer
Wrote and designed engaging content for
curriculum used in text books and activities.

2016-2017

Fun Guide App - Managing Editor
Created and executed app's content plan,
while also utilizing graphic design skills to
create promotional materials.